<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<RasytiLecture>
 <Title>Chinese (Zhuyin)</Title>
 <Comment>created by Daniel Schaefer</Comment>
 <Levels>

 <Level>
 <!-- 1 -->
 <NewCharacters>ㄎㄜ</NewCharacters>
 <Line>ㄜㄜ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄎㄜ ㄎㄜㄎㄎ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄜㄜ ㄎㄜㄎㄎ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄜㄜ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄜ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄎㄎㄎ</Line>
 <Line>ㄜ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄜ ㄎ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄎ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄎㄜ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄜ ㄜ ㄜㄎㄜ</Line>
 <Line>ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄜㄜ ㄎㄜ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄜ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄎㄜ ㄜㄎㄜ ㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄜ ㄎ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄎㄎ</Line>
 <Line>ㄜ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄜ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄎ ㄎ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄜ ㄎ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄜㄜ ㄜㄎㄜ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄜ ㄜ ㄜㄜ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄜ ㄜ</Line>
 <Line>ㄜㄜ ㄜ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄜ ㄎ ㄜㄎㄜ ㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄜ ㄎㄜ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄎ ㄎㄎㄎ</Line>
 <Line>ㄎㄜㄎ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄜ ㄜ ㄜㄎㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄜ ㄜ ㄎ ㄜㄎㄜ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄜ ㄎㄜ ㄎ ㄎㄜ ㄎ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄜ</Line>
 <Line>ㄎㄜㄎ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄎ ㄜ ㄎ ㄜ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄜ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄎ ㄜㄎㄜ ㄜ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄎ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄎ ㄜ ㄎㄜ ㄎ ㄜㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄎ</Line>
 <Line>ㄜㄎㄜ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄎ ㄜㄎㄜ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄜㄜ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄜ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄜ ㄜㄎㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄜ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄎ ㄜㄎㄎ</Line>
 <Line>ㄎㄎㄎ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄜ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄜ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄜㄜ ㄜ ㄎㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄜㄜ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄎ</Line>
 <Line>ㄎㄜㄜ ㄜㄎㄜ ㄜ ㄜ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄎ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄎ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄎㄜ ㄜ ㄜ ㄎ ㄜㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄎ ㄜㄎㄜ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄎㄎ</Line>
 <Line>ㄎㄎ ㄎㄜ ㄎ ㄜ ㄎ ㄜㄜ ㄎ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄜ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄎ ㄎㄜ ㄜㄎㄜ ㄎ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄜ</Line>
 <Line>ㄜㄎㄎ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄜ ㄜ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄎ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄎㄜ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄎㄜ ㄜ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄎ ㄎ</Line>
 <Line>ㄎㄎㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄜ ㄎ ㄜㄜ ㄜㄎㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄜㄜ ㄎㄜ ㄎ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄜ ㄜㄜ ㄜㄜ ㄎ ㄎㄜ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄜ</Line>
 <Line>ㄎㄜ ㄎ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄜㄜ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄜㄎ</Line>
 <Line>ㄎㄜㄜ ㄜ ㄜ ㄎ ㄎ ㄎ ㄜ ㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄜ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄎ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄜ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄜㄎㄜ ㄜㄜ ㄜ ㄎㄜ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ</Line>
 <Line>ㄜㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄎ ㄜ ㄎㄜ ㄜ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄜㄜ ㄎㄜ ㄜㄜ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄎㄜ ㄎ ㄜㄎㄜ ㄜ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄎ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄎㄎ</Line>
 <Line>ㄜ ㄎㄜ ㄜ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄎㄜ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄜ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄎ ㄎ ㄜ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄜ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄎ ㄜ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄜ ㄎ ㄎㄎ</Line>
 <Line>ㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄜ ㄜ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄜ ㄎ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄜ ㄜㄜ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄎㄜ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄎㄜ ㄎ ㄎㄜㄜ</Line>
 <Line>ㄜㄎㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄎㄜ ㄎ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄎ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄜㄜ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄜ ㄎ ㄜ ㄎ ㄜ ㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄜ ㄜㄎㄎ</Line>
 <Line>ㄎㄜ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄎ ㄜ ㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄜㄜ ㄎ ㄜㄎㄜ ㄜ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄜㄎㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄎ</Line>
 <Line>ㄜㄎㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄜ ㄎ ㄎ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄜ ㄜ ㄜ ㄜ ㄜㄎㄜ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ</Line>
 <Line>ㄎㄜㄜ ㄎ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄜㄜ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄎ ㄎ ㄜㄎㄜ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄎ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄜ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄜㄎㄜ</Line>
 <Line>ㄜㄎㄎ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄎ ㄎ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄎㄜ ㄜ ㄜ ㄎ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄜ ㄜㄜ ㄎ ㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄜㄎ</Line>
 <Line>ㄎㄜㄜ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄎㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄜ ㄎㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄜ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄎㄜ ㄎ ㄜ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄜㄜ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄎㄜ ㄜㄎㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ</Line>
 <Line>ㄜ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄜ ㄎ ㄜㄜ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄎ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄜ ㄎ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄎ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄜㄜ ㄎㄜ ㄎㄜ ㄜㄎㄎ</Line>
 <Line>ㄜㄜ ㄎ ㄜㄜ ㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄜㄜ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄎ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄜ ㄎㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄎ ㄎㄜㄎ</Line>
 <Line>ㄎㄎㄎ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄎㄜ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄎ ㄎ ㄎㄜ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄜ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄜㄜ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄜ ㄎ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄎㄜ ㄜ</Line>
 <Line>ㄎㄜㄜ ㄜㄎㄜ ㄎㄜ ㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄎ ㄜ ㄎ ㄜ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄜㄜ ㄎㄜ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄎㄜ ㄜㄜ ㄜㄜ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄜ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄎㄜㄎ</Line>
 <Line>ㄎ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄎㄜ ㄜ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄎ ㄜㄜ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄜ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄜ</Line>
 <Line>ㄎㄜㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄜ ㄜㄜ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ ㄎㄜㄜ ㄜ ㄎㄎㄎ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄎㄎ ㄎ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄜㄜ ㄜㄎㄎ ㄜㄜ ㄎ ㄜ ㄎㄎ ㄜㄎㄎㄜ</Line>
 </Level>
 
 <Level>
 <!-- 2 -->
 <NewCharacters>ㄨㄠ</NewCharacters>
 <Line>ㄨㄨㄠ ㄠㄨㄜㄠㄨ ㄠ ㄠㄠㄨㄠ ㄨㄜ ㄨㄠ ㄜ ㄠㄎ ㄜㄠㄨㄜ ㄠㄨ ㄜㄠㄜ ㄜ ㄨㄜㄠㄜㄠ ㄠㄎㄠㄜㄜㄠ ㄜㄠㄜ ㄠㄜㄠ ㄠㄎ ㄨㄜ ㄜ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄜㄠㄨ ㄠㄨㄠ ㄜㄠㄎㄠㄜㄜ ㄜㄠㄜ ㄠㄠㄨ ㄠ ㄠㄎㄠㄜㄜㄠ ㄠㄨ ㄜㄠㄜ ㄠㄨㄜㄠㄨ ㄜㄠㄜ ㄜ ㄠㄎㄠㄜㄜㄠ ㄠㄨㄠ ㄠㄠㄨ ㄠㄜㄠ ㄠㄠㄨ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄜㄠ ㄜㄠㄜ ㄜ ㄠㄎㄠㄜㄜㄠ ㄜ ㄨㄜ ㄜㄠㄜㄨㄨ ㄨㄠ ㄜ ㄨㄜㄠㄜㄠ ㄜㄠㄜ ㄜㄠㄜ ㄨㄠ ㄜ ㄠ ㄠㄜㄠ ㄨㄠ ㄜ ㄠㄎ ㄠ ㄠㄠㄨㄎ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠ ㄜㄠㄜ ㄜ ㄜ ㄠㄠㄨ ㄠㄠㄨ ㄠㄎ ㄜㄠㄜ ㄜㄠㄜ ㄠㄨ ㄨㄠ ㄠㄎ ㄨㄨㄠ ㄠ ㄠㄜㄠ ㄠㄎㄠㄜㄠ ㄜㄠㄜ ㄠㄨㄜㄠㄨ ㄠ ㄜㄠㄜ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄨㄠ ㄜ ㄜㄠㄜ ㄠ ㄠㄎ ㄜㄠㄜ ㄠㄠㄨ ㄠㄠㄨ ㄜㄠㄜ ㄠㄜㄠ ㄠㄎㄠㄜㄠ ㄠ ㄜ ㄨㄜ ㄨㄜㄠㄜㄠ ㄨㄠ ㄨㄨㄠㄜㄠ ㄠ ㄜㄠㄜ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄜㄠ ㄜㄠㄜ ㄠㄨㄠ ㄨㄠ ㄠㄜㄨㄠ ㄠㄎㄠㄜㄨㄠ ㄨㄠㄜㄨㄜ ㄠㄎ ㄠㄨㄠ ㄠㄨ ㄠㄜㄨㄠ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄠㄠㄨ ㄠㄎㄠㄜㄨㄠ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄠㄨㄨㄠㄨ</Line>
 <Line>ㄨㄠㄜ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄠ ㄨㄨㄠ ㄜ ㄜ ㄠㄎㄠㄜㄨㄠ ㄠ ㄠ ㄠㄜㄠ ㄠㄎ ㄠ ㄨㄨㄠ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄠㄨ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄜ ㄨㄜ ㄎㄠㄜㄎㄠ ㄠㄨ ㄠㄨ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄨㄠ ㄜ ㄨㄨㄠ ㄠㄨㄠ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄜ ㄨㄠㄨㄜ ㄜ ㄎㄠ ㄠㄨㄠㄨ ㄜㄠㄜ ㄨㄠ ㄠㄨㄠ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄠㄨㄠㄨ ㄠㄨ ㄜ ㄠㄨㄠㄎㄠ ㄨㄠ ㄠㄨㄠ</Line>
 <Line>ㄜㄠㄜ ㄠㄜㄠ ㄎㄠ ㄜ ㄠㄨ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄨㄨㄠ ㄨㄠㄨㄜ ㄠㄨ ㄠ ㄨㄠㄨㄜ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄜ ㄠㄨㄠㄨ ㄠㄨ ㄎㄠ ㄠㄜㄠ ㄠ ㄜ ㄎㄠ ㄜㄠㄜ</Line>
 <Line>ㄨㄠㄨㄜ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄠㄎㄠㄜㄨㄠ ㄎㄠ ㄠㄎㄠㄜㄨㄠ ㄎㄠ ㄠ ㄠㄨ ㄨㄠ ㄜ ㄨㄨㄠ ㄜ ㄠㄜㄨㄠ ㄠㄨㄠ ㄠㄜㄨㄠ ㄜ ㄠㄜㄠ ㄠ ㄨㄠ ㄠ</Line>
 <Line>ㄨㄠㄨㄜ ㄠㄎㄠㄜㄨㄠ ㄠㄨㄠㄎㄠ ㄜ ㄠ ㄠㄨㄨㄠㄨ ㄠㄨㄠ ㄜㄠㄜ ㄨㄠㄜㄨㄜ ㄠ ㄠㄨㄠㄨ ㄨㄜ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄨㄠ ㄨㄨㄠㄜㄠ ㄨㄠ ㄜㄠㄜ ㄠㄨㄠㄎㄠ</Line>
 <Line>ㄎㄠ ㄠㄜㄨㄠ ㄠㄨㄠㄎㄠ ㄨㄜ ㄨㄜ ㄨㄠ ㄠㄨ ㄠㄜㄨㄠ ㄜ ㄨㄠ ㄨㄨㄠㄜㄠ ㄠㄨㄨㄠㄨ ㄨㄠㄜㄨㄜ ㄜ ㄠㄜㄨㄠ ㄠㄨㄨㄠㄨ ㄠㄨㄠㄨ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄨ ㄨㄠ ㄨㄠ ㄎㄠ ㄎㄠ ㄨㄠ ㄎㄠ ㄠ ㄠㄜㄠ ㄠㄨㄠㄎㄠ ㄠㄨ ㄨㄠㄎㄠㄜㄜ ㄠㄨㄠㄎㄠ ㄎㄠ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄨㄨㄠ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄜ ㄜ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠ ㄠㄨㄠㄨ ㄠㄨㄨㄠㄨ ㄜ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄠㄜㄠ ㄠㄎㄠㄜㄨㄠ ㄠㄨㄠㄎㄠ ㄠㄨㄠㄎㄠ ㄜ ㄨㄠㄜㄨㄜ ㄠㄜㄨㄠ ㄨㄜ ㄠㄜㄠ ㄠㄨㄨㄠㄨ ㄨㄨㄠㄜㄠ</Line>
 <Line>ㄨㄠ ㄎㄠ ㄨㄜ ㄠㄨ ㄠㄜㄨㄠ ㄠㄜㄠ ㄎㄠ ㄜ ㄠ ㄜ ㄠㄨㄨㄠㄨ ㄠㄨㄨㄠㄨ ㄎㄠ ㄠㄨㄠㄎㄠ ㄠㄨㄠ ㄠㄨㄠㄎㄠ ㄜㄠㄜ ㄠㄨㄠㄎㄠ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄨ ㄨㄜ ㄠㄨㄠㄎㄠ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄠㄨ ㄠ ㄠㄨㄨㄠㄨ ㄠ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄠ ㄠㄠㄨ ㄨㄠㄜㄨㄨ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄨㄠ ㄨㄠㄎㄠㄜㄨ ㄠㄨㄠ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄠㄨㄨㄠㄨ</Line>
 <Line>ㄨㄠ ㄨㄨㄠㄜㄠ ㄠㄎㄠㄜㄨㄠ ㄨㄠㄜㄨㄨ ㄠㄎㄠㄜㄨㄠ ㄜㄠㄜ ㄎㄠ ㄠㄨㄠㄨ ㄜ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄠㄨㄠㄨ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄨㄜ ㄠㄨ ㄨㄠ ㄜ ㄜ ㄜㄠㄜ</Line>
 <Line>ㄜ ㄠㄨㄠㄨ ㄎㄠ ㄜ ㄨㄨㄠㄜㄠ ㄠ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄨㄜ ㄠ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄜ ㄠㄨㄠㄎㄠ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄠㄨㄠ ㄨㄨㄠ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄠㄜㄠ ㄎㄠ ㄠㄨㄠㄎㄠ</Line>
 <Line>ㄨㄠㄜ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄜㄠㄜ ㄠㄨㄨㄠㄨ ㄠㄨㄠㄨ ㄠㄨ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄎㄠ ㄠㄨㄠㄎㄠ ㄎㄠ ㄠㄜㄠ ㄨㄠㄜㄨㄨ ㄜ ㄠㄜㄨㄠ ㄠㄎㄠㄜㄨㄠ ㄜ ㄨㄨㄠㄜㄠ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠ ㄠㄨㄠㄨ ㄜ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄠㄨㄨㄠㄨ ㄠㄠㄨ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄠㄨㄠ ㄎㄠ ㄠ ㄠㄠㄨ ㄜ ㄠㄨ ㄠ ㄠㄨㄨㄠㄨ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄠㄨ ㄠㄜㄠ ㄠㄨㄠ</Line>
 <Line>ㄜㄠㄜ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄨㄠㄜ ㄠㄠㄨ ㄠㄜ ㄠㄨㄠㄨ ㄜ ㄠㄜㄠ ㄠㄎㄠㄜㄠ ㄠㄠㄎㄠ ㄜ ㄠㄜ ㄠㄜ ㄨㄠㄜㄠ ㄨㄜ ㄠㄠㄎㄠ ㄠㄨ ㄠㄠㄨ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄜ ㄠㄜㄠ ㄠㄜ ㄠㄠㄎaㄎ ㄨㄠ ㄠㄠㄨ ㄠ ㄠㄎㄠㄜㄠ ㄨㄠ ㄨㄨㄠ ㄠㄨ ㄠㄨㄜ ㄠㄨ ㄠㄜ ㄠㄜ ㄠㄠㄨ ㄠㄠㄎaㄎ ㄠㄨㄠㄨ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄎㄠㄜㄠ ㄠㄨ ㄨㄠ ㄨㄠㄜㄠ ㄠㄠㄎaㄎ ㄠ ㄠㄨㄠ ㄠㄜㄠ ㄠㄨㄠㄨ ㄠㄜ ㄠㄠㄨ ㄠㄜ ㄠㄨㄠㄨ ㄨㄜ ㄠㄜ ㄠㄠㄨ ㄠ ㄠㄜㄠ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠ ㄠ ㄨㄠ ㄠ ㄨㄠㄜㄠ ㄎaㄎ ㄨㄠ ㄜ ㄠㄠㄎaㄎ ㄠㄨ ㄠㄜㄠ ㄠㄜ ㄠㄜ ㄜ ㄠㄜㄠ ㄠㄨㄠ ㄠㄜ ㄨㄨㄠ ㄨㄨㄠ</Line>
 <Line>ㄜ ㄎaㄎ ㄎaㄎ ㄨㄠ ㄠㄜ ㄠㄜ ㄠㄜ ㄨㄠㄜㄠ ㄠㄨ ㄠ ㄠㄜ ㄠㄜ ㄠ ㄠㄜㄨㄨ ㄠㄜㄨㄠ ㄨㄨㄠ ㄠㄜㄠ ㄠㄨㄠㄨ ㄠㄜㄨㄠㄜ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄨㄠ ㄜ ㄠㄜ ㄜ ㄨㄠ ㄎaㄎ ㄠㄜㄠ ㄠㄨㄠ ㄜ ㄜㄠㄜ ㄠ ㄠㄨㄠ ㄜ ㄨㄨㄠ ㄜ ㄨㄠ ㄠㄠㄨ ㄠㄠㄨ ㄠㄜㄠ ㄨㄨㄠ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄜ ㄠㄨ ㄠ ㄨㄠ ㄠㄨㄠㄨ ㄨㄜ ㄠㄜ ㄠㄨㄜ ㄠ ㄜ ㄨㄠ ㄠㄜㄠ ㄠ ㄠㄜㄠ ㄠㄎㄠㄜㄜ ㄨㄠㄜㄠ ㄨㄨㄠ ㄨㄨㄠ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄜ ㄨㄠ ㄠㄜ ㄨㄜ ㄠㄠㄨ ㄠ ㄠㄜㄠㄨㄜ ㄜ ㄨㄨㄠ ㄨㄜ ㄠㄨㄜ ㄎaㄎ ㄠ ㄨㄠ ㄠㄨㄠㄨ ㄨㄠ ㄠㄠㄨ ㄨㄜ ㄠㄎㄠㄜㄠ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄎㄠㄜㄜ ㄠㄜ ㄠㄜ ㄠㄠㄎaㄎ ㄠㄜ ㄠㄠㄨ ㄨㄠ ㄎaㄎ ㄨㄜ ㄠㄠㄨ ㄠㄨㄜ ㄠㄨ ㄨㄠㄜㄠ ㄠㄜ ㄠㄨ ㄨㄠ ㄠㄨ ㄨㄠ ㄜ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄠㄎaㄎ ㄠ ㄠㄜㄠ aㄎa ㄠㄜ ㄠㄜ ㄨㄜ ㄠㄠaㄎa ㄠㄜ ㄠㄜㄠ ㄠㄨㄜ ㄨㄜ ㄜ ㄨㄜ ㄠㄨㄠ ㄠㄨㄠㄨ ㄠㄜ aㄎa ㄨㄠ</Line>
 </Level>
 
 <!-- TODO: Need to add ㄤ -->
 <Level>
 <!-- 3 -->
 <NewCharacters>ㄋ</NewCharacters>
 <Line>ㄠㄨㄜㄋㄎㄠ ㄠㄨㄜㄠ ㄠ ㄋㄠㄨㄋ ㄠㄨㄜㄋ ㄎㄠㄜㄋ ㄠㄨㄋf ㄜㄠ ㄠㄋㄎㄜ ㄠㄋ ㄠㄋ ㄠㄋ ㄠㄜㄨ ㄋㄠㄜ ㄜㄋ ㄨㄠ ㄨㄨㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠ ㄋㄠㄨ ㄨㄠ ㄠㄜㄨ ㄠㄋㄎㄜ fㄜㄋㄎㄠㄋ ㄎㄜ ㄠㄋㄎㄜ ㄠㄋㄎㄜ ㄠㄋㄎㄎㄠㄜ ㄨㄨㄠㄋㄎㄜ ㄠㄨㄜ ㄠㄨㄜㄋㄎㄠㄋ ㄠㄨㄋㄎㄜ ㄠㄨ</Line>
 <Line>ㄜㄠ ㄠㄨ ㄠㄨ ㄠㄜㄨ ㄠㄨㄋㄎㄜ ㄠㄋㄎㄜ ㄠㄨㄋㄎㄜ ㄨㄋ ㄠㄋ ㄜㄠ ㄨㄠ ㄨㄠ ㄠㄋㄎㄜ ㄠㄨㄋㄎㄜㄜㄋㄎㄠㄋㄠㄨㄋ ㄨㄋ ㄜㄠ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄋㄎㄜ ㄠㄠ ㄠㄋㄋ ㄠㄨㄎㄜㄋ ㄋㄠㄨㄋf ㄠㄋㄋ ㄠㄎㄜㄋ ㄨㄠ ㄜㄠ ㄠㄋㄠㄨㄋㄠㄨ ㄜㄠ ㄠㄎㄜㄋf ㄜㄠ ㄠㄋㄋㄠㄨㄋ ㄠㄋ ㄨㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄋ ㄠㄎㄜㄋ ㄜㄜ ㄨㄋ ㄜㄠ ㄨㄋ ㄠㄋ ㄠㄨㄎㄜㄋ ㄨㄠ ㄨㄨㄠㄎㄜㄋ ㄠㄎㄜㄋ ㄨㄨㄠㄎㄜㄋ ㄠㄎㄜㄋfㄜㄋㄎㄠㄎㄜㄋ ㄠㄎㄜㄋㄜ ㄋㄠㄨ</Line>
 <Line>ㄋㄠㄨ ㄠㄨ ㄠㄨㄎㄜㄋ ㄠㄜㄨㄜㄋㄎㄠㄎㄜㄋf ㄠㄎㄜㄎ ㄋㄜㄜ ㄠㄋㄠㄨㄋ ㄠㄨ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋㄜ ㄠㄜㄋ ㄠㄨ ㄠㄜㄋ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋㄜ</Line>
 <Line>ㄋㄠㄨ ㄜㄠ ㄋf ㄠㄎㄜㄜ ㄠㄨ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋ ㄠㄨ ㄋㄠㄨ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋㄠㄨㄋ ㄋㄠㄨㄋ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋ ㄜㄋ ㄜㄋㄠㄨㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋ ㄠㄋㄠㄨㄋ ㄋf ㄠㄜㄋ ㄠㄨ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋf ㄠㄜㄋㄠㄨㄋ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋㄠㄨㄋ ㄨㄨㄋ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋ ㄋㄠㄜ ㄜㄠ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋf</Line>
 <Line>ㄋ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋㄜ ㄜㄋㄎㄨㄠ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋ ㄠㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋㄜ ㄨㄋ ㄠㄋㄠㄨㄋ ㄋㄠㄨㄋㄠㄨ ㄠㄜㄋ ㄠㄨㄎㄜㄎㄋ ㄨㄠ</Line>
 <Line>ㄜㄋ ㄠㄋ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋㄜㄜ ㄠㄎㄜ ㄜㄠ ㄜㄋ ㄜㄠ ㄨㄋ ㄜㄠ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋㄜ ㄜㄠ ㄠㄎㄜ ㄋㄠㄜ ㄠㄎㄜㄎ ㄋㄜㄜ ㄠㄜㄨ ㄋㄠㄨ ㄠㄜㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋ ㄠㄜㄋㄠㄨㄋ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋf ㄠㄎㄜㄎ ㄜㄜ ㄠㄋㄠㄨㄋ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋㄜ ㄋㄠㄜ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋㄋ ㄠㄜㄨ ㄠㄜㄨㄜㄋㄎㄨㄨㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄨㄜㄋㄎㄜㄠ ㄋㄠㄜ ㄨㄨㄋ ㄠㄎㄜ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋ ㄠㄋㄠㄨㄋf ㄋㄠㄨ ㄠㄎㄜㄎ ㄋㄜㄜ ㄨㄠ ㄠㄨ ㄜㄠ ㄠㄨ ㄨㄠㄜㄋㄎㄠ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄜㄨ ㄠㄜㄨ ㄠㄎㄜ ㄠㄜㄨ ㄜㄠ ㄠㄨ ㄠㄨ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋ ㄠㄨ ㄠㄜㄋ ㄠㄎㄜㄎ ㄋㄜㄜ ㄜㄠㄜㄋㄎㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋㄜ ㄠㄨ ㄠㄨ ㄜㄋ ㄜㄠ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋf ㄨㄋㄠㄨㄋㄠㄜ ㄠㄨㄎ ㄜㄎㄋ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋㄋ ㄠㄎㄜ ㄎㄋㄜ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋ ㄠㄎ ㄜㄎ ㄋㄜㄜ ㄨㄨㄋ ㄠㄜㄨ ㄋㄠㄜ ㄨㄠ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠ ㄠㄨ ㄨㄨㄋ ㄠㄋ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋㄜ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋ ㄜㄠ ㄋㄠㄨ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋf ㄜㄠ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋㄜㄜ ㄋㄠㄜ ㄨㄨㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋㄠㄨㄋf ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋ ㄜㄜ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄨㄎㄜㄎㄋ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋㄠㄨㄋ ㄠㄋ ㄠㄎㄜ ㄎㄋㄜㄜ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋ ㄜㄠ ㄨㄠ ㄜㄠ ㄠㄨ ㄠㄋ ㄜㄠ ㄠㄋ ㄜㄠ ㄋf ㄠㄠㄋ ㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋㄜㄜ ㄜㄠ</Line>
 <Line>ㄋf ㄠㄨ ㄜㄋ ㄠㄜㄨ ㄠㄨ ㄨㄨㄠㄎㄜㄎㄋ ㄠㄎㄋㄜ ㄠㄋ ㄨㄨㄠㄎㄋ ㄠㄎㄋㄜㄜ ㄠㄎㄋㄜㄜ ㄠㄎㄋㄜ ㄋㄠㄨㄋf ㄋㄠㄨ ㄠㄎㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄨㄋ ㄠㄎㄋf ㄠㄨㄎㄋ ㄠㄎㄋf ㄠㄜㄋ ㄜㄋ ㄠㄎㄋ ㄨㄨㄠㄎㄋㄠㄨㄋㄠㄨ ㄠㄨㄎㄋ ㄠㄎㄋㄜ ㄜㄋㄎㄨㄋㄠ ㄨㄨㄠㄎㄋ ㄠㄨㄋㄜ ㄋㄎㄜㄋ ㄠㄎㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄎㄋ ㄠㄜㄨ ㄠㄎㄋㄋ ㄠㄎㄋㄜ ㄠㄋ ㄠㄨ ㄠㄎㄋㄜ ㄠㄋㄋ ㄨㄠ ㄋf ㄠㄨㄎㄋ ㄜㄠ ㄋㄠㄨㄋ ㄠㄎㄋ ㄠㄋㄎfㄜㄋㄎㄠㄜㄋ ㄠㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄋ ㄠㄋㄎㄋㄠㄨㄠㄨ ㄠㄋㄎㄜㄜ ㄨㄠㄠㄋㄠㄜ ㄋf ㄠㄜㄋ ㄠㄜㄋㄠㄨ ㄠㄋㄎㄜ ㄨㄠ ㄠㄜㄋㄠㄠㄋㄎ ㄜㄜㄠㄜㄋㄠㄨ</Line>
 <Line>ㄜㄋ ㄠㄜㄋ ㄜㄋ ㄠㄨㄋㄎ ㄠㄋㄎㄋ ㄠㄋㄋ ㄠㄋㄎㄜ ㄜㄠㄜㄋㄎㄜㄋ ㄠㄜㄋㄠㄨㄠㄜ ㄠㄨ ㄋㄠㄨ ㄠㄋㄎㄋ ㄠㄨㄜㄋㄎㄨㄋ ㄨㄨㄋㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄜㄠ ㄠㄜㄋㄠㄨ ㄠㄨ ㄋㄠㄨㄜㄋㄎ ㄠㄋㄎf ㄠㄋㄠㄨf ㄠㄋ ㄠㄋㄎ ㄋㄠㄨf ㄠㄋㄎㄋ ㄠㄋㄋ ㄨㄨㄠㄋㄎㄠ ㄋㄠㄜ ㄠㄋㄎㄜ</Line>
 <Line>ㄋ ㄜㄠ ㄠㄋㄎ ㄠㄋㄎ ㄜㄠ ㄠㄋㄎ ㄠㄨ ㄨㄨㄋㄋ ㄠㄋ ㄠㄋㄎf ㄠㄋㄎ ㄨㄨㄋㄋ ㄜㄠ ㄠㄋㄎ ㄨㄨㄠㄋㄎ ㄨㄨㄋ ㄋf ㄠㄋㄎ</Line>
 <Line>ㄨㄨㄠㄋㄎ ㄜㄋ ㄠㄋㄎ ㄨㄋㄠ ㄋㄠㄨ ㄨㄨㄠㄋㄎ ㄠㄨ ㄋf ㄠㄜㄨ ㄜㄠㄜㄋㄎㄨㄨㄠㄋㄎ ㄜㄋㄠㄨ ㄠㄋㄎㄋ ㄠㄋ ㄠㄨ ㄋㄠㄜ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄋㄎㄠ ㄋㄠㄨ ㄠㄨ ㄠㄋ ㄨㄋ ㄠㄜㄨ ㄠㄨㄋㄎ ㄜㄋ ㄠㄜㄨ ㄜㄋ ㄠㄋㄎㄜ ㄨㄨㄋ ㄠㄋㄎ ㄠㄋㄎㄠ ㄜㄠ ㄨㄋ ㄠㄨ</Line>
 <Line>ㄋ ㄠㄋㄠㄨ ㄋㄠㄨf ㄠㄋㄎㄋ ㄨㄠ ㄠㄨㄋㄎㄠ ㄠㄜㄨ ㄠㄋ ㄨㄠ ㄠㄋ ㄠㄨ ㄋㄠㄜ ㄠㄋㄎf ㄨㄨㄠㄋㄎㄠ ㄜㄋ ㄠㄨ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄨㄋㄎ ㄠㄜㄨ ㄨㄋㄠㄨ ㄨㄋ ㄠㄋㄎ ㄋㄠㄜ ㄠㄋㄎ ㄋㄜㄜ ㄨㄠ ㄜㄋㄠ ㄠㄋㄎㄋㄋ ㄠㄋㄎㄋ ㄠㄜㄨ ㄠㄋㄎㄋ ㄨㄨㄋ ㄠㄋㄎㄋ ㄨㄨㄋ ㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄋㄜㄋ ㄎㄜㄠ ㄠㄋㄎㄋㄜ ㄠㄋㄎㄋㄋ ㄠㄨㄜㄋㄎㄠ ㄋㄎㄋf ㄜㄠ ㄋf ㄋㄠㄨ ㄜㄠ ㄋf ㄠㄜㄨ ㄠㄋㄠㄨㄠㄜ ㄠㄋ ㄠㄋ ㄠㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄨ ㄋf ㄜㄠ ㄠㄋㄎ ㄜㄠ ㄠㄋㄎ ㄨㄨㄋ ㄠㄋㄎㄋ ㄜㄠ ㄠㄨㄋㄎ ㄨㄨㄠㄋㄎ ㄠㄨ ㄨㄋ ㄨㄠ ㄋf ㄜㄠ ㄜㄠ ㄨㄠ ㄨㄠ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄋㄎf ㄠㄋㄎ ㄠㄋㄎㄋ ㄠㄋㄎㄋㄠㄨ ㄠㄋㄎ ㄋㄠㄜ ㄠㄜㄋㄠㄨㄠㄨ ㄠㄜㄨ ㄠㄨㄋㄎ ㄜㄠ ㄜㄋㄠㄨ ㄠㄨ ㄜㄠ ㄠㄋㄎㄜ ㄠㄋㄎ ㄠ</Line>
 </Level>
 
 <Level>
 <!-- 4 -->
 <NewCharacters>ㄇㄑ</NewCharacters>
 <Line>ㄎㄠㄠ ㄎㄇㄑㄋ ㄋㄠㄎㄜㄋ ㄑㄠㄎㄜ ㄑㄇㄑㄋ ㄑㄇㄑ ㄑㄠㄎㄜ ㄋㄇㄑㄋ ㄑㄠㄎㄋㄜ ㄨㄎㄜㄇㄑ ㄑㄠㄎㄜ</Line>
 <Line>ㄋㄎㄋ ㄇㄑㄠ ㄋㄇㄑㄎ ㄨㄎㄜㄇㄑㄋ ㄇㄑ ㄠㄇㄑㄋ ㄑㄠㄎㄜㄋ ㄇㄑㄠㄎ ㄠㄎ ㄎㄋㄜ ㄑㄠㄎㄜ ㄠㄎㄜㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄎㄋㄜ ㄇㄑ ㄨㄎㄜㄑㄇ ㄑㄎㄋ ㄠㄎ ㄋㄑㄇ ㄋㄎㄋ ㄜㄎㄋ ㄜㄎ ㄑㄑㄇ ㄑㄑㄇ ㄑㄇㄨ ㄑㄎ ㄜ ㄠㄑㄇ</Line>
 <Line>ㄨㄎㄜ ㄠㄎㄋ ㄠㄑㄇ ㄋㄑㄇㄠ ㄑㄇ ㄨㄎㄜㄑㄇ ㄑㄇ ㄑㄇㄋ ㄋㄎㄜ ㄑㄇㄎㄋ ㄋㄑㄇㄠ ㄠㄎㄋ ㄑㄠㄎㄜ</Line>
 <Line>ㄑㄇㄑㄑㄇㄑㄎ ㄑㄇㄠㄜㄋㄎㄨㄎㄜ ㄑㄇㄑㄇ ㄠㄎㄜ ㄠㄎㄋ ㄠㄑㄇ ㄠㄎㄜㄎ ㄑㄑㄇㄋ ㄑㄇㄎㄜㄋ ㄑㄇㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄑㄇㄋ ㄑㄠㄎㄜ ㄑㄇㄠ ㄋㄑ ㄋㄑㄇㄠㄋ ㄨㄎㄜㄋ ㄨㄎㄜㄑㄇㄋ ㄎㄋㄑㄇ ㄎㄋㄜ ㄑㄇㄋ ㄎㄨ ㄑㄇㄠ ㄑㄇㄠㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄎㄜㄎ ㄋㄑㄇㄠ ㄎㄠㄠㄎ ㄋㄎㄠㄋㄎㄋ ㄎㄠㄠㄋ ㄋㄎ ㄎㄠㄋ ㄋㄎㄠㄎㄠㄋ ㄑㄑㄇㄋ ㄎㄋㄜ ㄑㄇㄠㄋ ㄎㄋㄜㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄋㄎㄋ ㄨㄎㄜㄑㄇ ㄠㄎㄜㄋ ㄠㄎㄋ ㄠㄑㄇ ㄎㄜ ㄠㄑㄇ ㄋㄠㄎㄜ ㄑㄑㄇㄠ ㄑㄇㄑㄑㄇㄑㄎㄋ ㄋㄠㄎㄜㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄑㄑㄇ ㄑㄇ ㄠㄑㄇ ㄑㄇ ㄑㄇㄠㄎ ㄑㄇ ㄋㄑㄇ ㄋㄑㄇㄑㄇㄋ ㄋㄜㄎ ㄋㄑㄇㄑㄇ ㄑㄠㄎㄜ ㄋㄜㄎㄋㄎ ㄨㄎㄜㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄎㄋㄑㄇ ㄑㄇㄋ ㄑㄇ ㄑㄠㄎㄜ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄑㄇㄎㄎ ㄠㄑㄇ ㄑㄇㄎㄜㄋ ㄜ ㄨㄎㄜㄑㄇ ㄑㄑㄇㄠ ㄑㄎㄋ ㄋㄑㄇㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄑㄇㄠ ㄑㄇㄠㄎ ㄑㄇㄑㄑㄇㄑㄎㄋ ㄑㄇㄑ ㄑㄑㄇㄠㄋ ㄑㄠㄎㄜ ㄠㄎㄜ ㄑㄠㄎㄜ ㄑㄠㄎㄜㄋ ㄎㄋㄜㄋ ㄑㄠㄎㄜ ㄠㄎㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄑㄠㄎㄜ ㄠㄎㄋ ㄠㄎ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄑㄠㄎㄋㄜㄋ ㄑㄇㄎ ㄋㄜㄎㄋ ㄋㄑㄇ ㄎㄜㄋㄎ ㄋㄑㄇ ㄠㄎ ㄋㄜㄎㄋ ㄋㄑㄇㄠ</Line>
 <Line>ㄋㄎㄋ ㄠㄑㄇㄋ ㄎㄋㄑㄇㄋ ㄑㄇㄠ ㄋㄑㄇ ㄑㄇㄠ ㄠㄑㄇㄋ ㄜㄑㄇ ㄋㄑㄇㄋㄎ ㄋㄠㄎㄜ ㄎㄋㄑㄇㄋ ㄠㄑㄇㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄑㄇㄠ ㄑㄇㄑㄑㄇㄑㄎ ㄋㄎㄜ ㄑㄇㄑㄑㄇㄑㄎㄋ ㄑㄑㄇㄠㄋ ㄎㄋㄜ ㄑㄎㄋ ㄑㄇㄠㄋ ㄎㄋㄜㄋ ㄠㄎㄋ ㄨㄎㄜ</Line>
 <Line>ㄎㄋㄜㄋ ㄑㄇㄠㄋ ㄇㄑㄎㄜ ㄇㄑㄠㄋ ㄇㄑㄎㄜㄋ ㄇㄑㄋ ㄎㄋㄜㄋㄜㄋㄎㄜ ㄨㄎㄜㄇㄑ ㄠㄎㄋ ㄑㄠㄎㄜ ㄎㄋㄇㄑㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄎ ㄑㄇㄑㄠ ㄇㄑ ㄜ ㄜㄇㄑ ㄇㄑㄑㄇㄑㄑㄎ ㄇㄑㄎ ㄑㄠㄎㄜㄋ ㄋㄎㄜㄋ ㄇㄑㄎㄋㄎ ㄠㄇㄑ ㄋㄇㄑㄋㄎㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄋㄎ ㄋㄜㄎㄋ ㄠㄇㄑㄋ ㄨㄎㄜㄎㄋ ㄇㄑ ㄇㄑㄑㄇㄑㄑㄎㄋ ㄠㄎㄜㄋ ㄋㄜㄎ ㄇㄑㄎㄜ ㄑㄠㄎㄜㄋ ㄎㄋ ㄋㄜㄎ</Line>
 <Line>ㄇㄑㄋ ㄨㄎㄜㄎㄋ ㄇㄑㄎ ㄑㄠㄎㄜ ㄑㄇㄑㄠㄋ ㄇㄑㄋ ㄑㄇㄑ ㄋㄇㄑㄋ ㄠㄎ ㄇㄑㄋ ㄎㄋㄜ ㄇㄑㄠㄎㄋ ㄋㄇㄑㄠㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄇㄑㄋ ㄋㄜㄎㄋ ㄋㄇㄑㄋㄎㄋ ㄑㄇㄑㄠ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄋㄇㄑㄋㄎ ㄑㄠㄎㄜ ㄇㄑㄠㄋ ㄑㄠㄎㄜㄋ ㄠㄎㄋ ㄋㄇㄑㄇㄑㄋㄜㄋㄎㄋㄇㄑㄋㄎㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄎㄜㄋ ㄑㄠㄎㄜ ㄋㄎㄜㄋ ㄋㄎㄋ ㄠㄎㄋ ㄇㄑ ㄑㄠㄎㄜㄋ ㄨㄎㄜㄋ ㄎㄨ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄇㄑㄎㄜ ㄑㄠㄎㄜㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄑㄠㄎㄜ ㄎㄋㄜ ㄠㄇㄑ ㄑㄠㄎㄜㄋ ㄇㄑㄋ ㄜㄇㄑ ㄇㄑ ㄨㄎㄜㄎㄋ ㄇㄑㄋ ㄎㄋㄜㄋ ㄇㄑㄎ ㄇㄑㄠㄎㄋ ㄨㄎㄜㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄇㄑㄑㄇㄑㄑㄎ ㄋㄎ ㄑㄠㄎㄜ ㄋㄇㄑㄋㄎ ㄎㄜㄋ ㄋㄎㄋ ㄠㄇㄑ ㄜㄠ ㄑㄎ ㄎㄋㄜㄋ ㄇㄑ ㄋㄇㄑㄠ</Line>
 <Line>ㄇㄑㄠㄎㄋ ㄑㄇㄑㄠ ㄠㄎㄜㄋ ㄇㄑㄠ ㄑㄇㄑㄠㄋ ㄋㄇㄑㄇㄑㄋ ㄇㄑㄠㄎ ㄋㄜㄎㄋ ㄇㄑㄠㄋ ㄇㄑㄠㄋ ㄨㄎㄜㄇㄑㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄎㄋㄜㄋ ㄋㄇㄑㄠㄋ ㄠㄎㄋ ㄠㄇㄑ ㄠㄎㄋ ㄎㄋㄜ ㄇㄑㄎㄜㄋ ㄜㄇㄑ ㄨㄎㄜ ㄑㄠㄎㄜ ㄋㄎㄠㄎㄠㄋ ㄑㄠㄎㄜㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄑㄎㄋ ㄋㄎㄜㄋ ㄋㄎㄠㄋㄎ ㄨㄎㄜㄎㄋㄎ ㄎㄠㄑㄎㄠㄑㄎ ㄠㄎㄠ ㄎㄠㄠㄋ ㄎㄠㄨ ㄠㄎㄠㄋ ㄠㄎㄜㄋ ㄑㄎㄠㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄑㄎㄠㄠ ㄑㄠㄎㄜㄋ ㄋㄎㄇㄎㄠ ㄠㄎㄠㄋ ㄎㄠㄠ ㄎㄠㄠㄎㄋㄠ ㄎㄠㄠㄎ ㄜ ㄠㄎㄠ ㄋㄜㄎ ㄠㄎㄜㄋ ㄎㄋㄜㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄎㄜ ㄨㄎㄜㄎㄇㄎ ㄑㄎ ㄎㄇㄎㄋ ㄠㄎㄠ ㄨㄎㄜㄎㄋ ㄎㄇㄎㄜ ㄠㄎㄋ ㄋㄠㄎㄜ ㄎㄠ ㄜㄎ ㄎㄋㄎㄠㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄋㄎㄠㄠ ㄎㄠㄠ ㄜ ㄑㄠㄎㄜ ㄎㄠㄋ ㄋㄠㄎㄜ ㄎㄠ ㄠㄎㄠ ㄠㄎㄠ ㄑㄎㄠ ㄎㄋㄜ ㄎㄠㄠ ㄎㄇㄎㄜㄋ ㄋㄎㄠㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄠㄎㄜㄋ ㄠㄎㄋ ㄑㄎㄠㄠㄋ ㄠㄎㄠㄋㄎ ㄠㄎㄋ ㄎㄜㄎ ㄠㄎㄜ ㄋㄜㄎㄋ ㄎㄠㄑ ㄎㄠ ㄨㄎㄜ ㄋㄠㄎㄜㄋ</Line>
 <Line>ㄋㄎㄇㄎㄠㄋ ㄎㄠㄠㄋ ㄠㄎㄠㄋ ㄋㄎㄇㄎㄠ ㄑㄠㄎㄜㄋㄜㄋㄎㄎㄠㄠㄜㄋㄎㄠㄎ ㄑㄎㄠ ㄋㄎ ㄠㄎㄠㄋ ㄑㄠㄎㄜ ㄎㄋ</Line>
 </Level>
 
 </Levels>
</RasytiLecture>
